A Guide to the Papers of Julian Bond, 1897-2006
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series VI: Political Papers
  - Subseries A: General
    - Atlanta Elections- Maps of Districts, etc. and Voting Districts, n.d. (Box-folder 81:7)
    - Atlanta, Georgia Politics- Sandy Springs Incident, 1971 (Box-folder 81:8)
    - Bill (H.R. 19) Challenging the Seating of Representative-Elect Julian Bond, 136th District, 1966 (Box-folder 81:9)
    - Bills, ca. 1968-1971, 1976 (Box-folder 81:10)
    - Bills- Sickle Cell Anemia, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 81:11)
    - Bills- Sickle Cell Anemia, ca. 1971-1972 (Box-folder 81:12)
    - Black Elected Officials, 1969-1972, 1976 (Box-folder 82:1)
    - Black Elected Officials- Letters concerning McGovern, etc., 1972 (Box-folder 82:2)
    - Black Georgians for McGovern-Shriver, 1972 (Box-folder 82:3)
    - Black Politics- Black Political Strategy for 197[0s], 1971-1972 (Box-folder 82:4)
    - Black Politics- Gary, Indiana Meeting Fall 1971, etc., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 82:5)
    - Black Politics- Mobile Meeting Fall 1971, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 82:6)
    - Black Politics- Chicago, Illinois Meeting, September 24, 1971 (Working File), 1972 (Box-folder 82:7)
    - Black Politics- Requests for Endorsements, etc., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 82:8)
    - A Black Strategy for George McGovern, n.d. (Box-folder 82:9)
    - Campaign- James G. Bond- Finance Material, 1975, 1977 (Box-folder 82:10)
    - Campaign- James G. Bond- Finance Material, 1981 (Box-folder 82:11)
    - Campaign- Julian Bond- Campaign Fund, 1967, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 83:1)
    - Campaign- Julian Bond- Campaign Fund, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 83:2)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Campaign Fund, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 83:3)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Congressional, n.d. (Box-folder 83:4)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Financial Disclosure, 1974 (Box-folder 83:5)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Financial Disclosure, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 83:6)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Financial Disclosure, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 83:7)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Georgia Senate- Contributions, 1976, 1984 (Box-folder 83:8)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Georgia Senate- Expenditures, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 83:9)
    - Campaign- Julian Bond- Materials for Campaigns, 1965-1986 (Box-folder 83:10)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Notice of Candidacy, 1972 (Box-folder 83:11)
    - Campaign - Julian Bond- Potential Contributors, 1992 (Box-folder 83:12)
    - Campaign- Julian Bond- Volunteers, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 83:13)
    - Campaign- Michael Julian Bond, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 84:1)
    - Campaign- Carter-Mondale Presidential, 1971, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 84:2)
    - Campaign- Maynard Jackson (including a Memorial Program), 1990, 2003, n.d. (Box-folder 84:3)
    - Campaign- Edward Kennedy, 1980 (Box-folder 84:4)
    - Campaign- C.B. King for Governor, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 84:5)
    - Campaign- Zell Miller, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 84:6)
    - Campaign- Herman Talmadge, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 84:7)
    - Campaign- Morris K. Udall, 1975-1976, 2 folders. (Box-folder 84:8-8a)
    - Campaign- Morris K. Udall- Background, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 84:9)
    - Campaign- Morris K. Udall- Expenses and Franklin Records, 1978, n.d. (Box-folder 84:10)
    - Campaign - Morris K. Udall- Position Statements, etc., 1975-1976 (Box-folder 84:11)
    - Campaign- Andrew Young for Congress, Governor, 1970, 1990 (Box-folder 84:12)
    - Campaign Bumper Stickers, 1976 (Box-folder 84:13)
    - Campaign Cards- Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box-folder 84:14)
    - Campaign Financial Disclosure (General), 1976 (Box-folder 85:1)
    - Campaign- Literature for Miscellaneous Other Candidates, 1965-1992 (Box-folder 85:2)
    - Congressional Black Caucus, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 85:3)
    - Correspondence concerning the 5th District of Georgia Race to replace Andrew Young, 1977 (Box-folder 85:4)
    - Correspondence with members of Congress concerning a brochure relating the campaign experiences of Southern black candidates, 1969 (Box-folder 85:5)
    - Correspondence with members of Congress and other Elected Officials concerning Bills and Nominations, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 85:6)
      Including Edward W. Brooke, Howard W. Cannon, Alan Cranston, Thomas J. Dodd, Charles E. Goodell, Philip A. Hart, Vance Hartke, Daniel K. Inouye, George McGovern, Walter F. Mondale, Edmund S. Muskie, William Proxmire, Abe Ribicoff, William B. Saxbe, Richard S. Schweiker, Joseph D. Tydings, and Stephen M. Young.
    - Democratic National Committee, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 85:7)
    - Democratic National Committee- Commission on Rules, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 85:8)
    - Democratic National Committee- McGovern Commission, 1969 (Box-folder 85:9)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box-folder 85:10)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1971 (Box-folder 85:11)
    - Democratic National Convention- Challenge to Method of Electing At-Large Georgia Delegates, 1971-1972, Working File. (Box-folder 86:1)
    - Democratic National Convention- Correspondence concerning, 1968, 1976 (Box-folder 86:2)
    - Democratic National Convention- Delegate Selection (March 11th Election), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 86:3)
    - Democratic National Convention- Delegate Selection (March 11th Election), 1972 (Box-folder 86:4)
    - Democratic National Convention- Delegate Selection Challenge, 1972 (Box-folder 86:5)
    - Democratic National Convention- Delegate Selection Correspondence, including Senator Edmund Muskie, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 86:6)
    - Democratic National Convention- Lists, 1969, 1972 (Box-folder 86:7)
    - Democratic National Convention- Lists, 1969, 1972 (Box-folder 86:8)
    - Democratic National Convention- "Negro Delegates and Alternates concerning 1968 Convention", 1968 (Box-folder 86:9)
    - Democratic National Convention- Uncommitted Black Delegates, 1972 (Box-folder 87:1)
    - Democratic Party of Georgia, 1968-1970, 1975 (Box-folder 87:2)
    - Democratic Party of Georgia- Forum, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 87:3)
    - Democratic Party- National, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 87:4)
    - Election of Julian Bond- First for the Georgia House of Representatives, 1965-1966, Chiefly news clippings. (Box-folder 87:5)
    - Election of Julian Bond- Second for the Georgia House of Representatives, 1966 (Box-folder 87:6)
    - Endorsement of Candidates, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 87:7)
    - Fulton County Democratic Party, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 87:8)
    - Fulton County House Delegation, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 87:9)
    - Fulton County, Georgia Street Index, 1972 (Box-folder 87:10)
    - Georgia Citizens for McGovern, 1972 (Box-folder 87:11)
    - Georgia Delegate Election for the Democratic National Convention, 1972 (Box-folder 87:12)
    - Georgia Democratic Executive Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 88:1)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 32, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 88:2)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 111, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 88:3)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 111- Correspondence and Newsletter, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 88:4)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 111- Correspondence and Newsletter, 1969 (Box-folder 88:5)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 111- Correspondence and Newsletter, 1970 (Box-folder 88:6)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 111- Correspondence and Newsletter, 1971 January-May (Box-folder 88:7)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 111- Correspondence and Newsletter, 1971 June-1972 (Box-folder 88:8)
    - Georgia House of Representatives District 111- Newsletter Material, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 88:9)
    - Georgia House of Representatives- Laboratory Licensing Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 89:1)
    - Georgia Politics, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 89:2)
    - Georgia Politics- Complaint concerning Election Law by Julian Bond and Andrew Young, 1971 (Box-folder 89:3)
    - Georgia Primaries, 1972 (Box-folder 89:4)
    - Georgia Reapportionment Challenge, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 89:5)
    - Georgia Reapportionment Challenge, 1971 (Box-folder 89:6)
    - Georgia Reapportionment District 111 (New 32), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 89:7)
    - Georgia Selection of Delegates to the 1972 Presidential Convention, 1972 (Box-folder 89:8)
    - Georgia State Senate, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 89:9)
    - Georgia State Senate Resolution 160 concerning Lt. Henry Ossian Flipper, 1977 March 3 (Box-folder 89:10)
    - Georgia Voter Registration Information, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 89:11)
    - Lowndes County [Alabama] Freedom Organization, 1966 (Box-folder 89:12)
    - McGovern-Shriver Campaign Banner, 1972, Oversize.
    - McGovern-Shriver State Coordinators, 1972 (Box-folder 90:1)
    - Manuscript by F. Parker Hudson concerning his first-hand account of the 1968 Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box-folder 90:2)
    - Manuscript by F. Parker Hudson concerning his first-hand account of the 1968 Democratic National Convention, n.d. (Box-folder 90:3)
    - Mississippi and Integration, 1958-1990 (Box-folder 90:4)
    - Mississippi Sovereignty Commission- Documents Online (Sovereignty Commission Online), ca. 2004 (Box-folder 90:5)
    - Mississippi Sovereignty Commission- Documents Online (Sovereignty Commission Online), ca. 2004 (Box-folder 90:6)
    - Mississippi Sovereignty Commission- Documents Online (Sovereignty Commission Online), ca. 2004 (Box-folder 90:7)
    - National Democratic Party of Alabama, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 90:8)
    - National Democratic Party of Alabama 1969 Credentials Brief filed before the Credentials Committee of the Democratic National Committee, 1989 (Box-folder 90:9)
    - National Black Political Association, 1976 (Box-folder 90:10)
    - National Politics, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 90:11)
    - National Politics, 1972 (Box-folder 90:12)
    - National Politics, 1973 (Box-folder 91:1)
    - National Politics, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 91:2)
    - National Politics- Finances, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 91:3)
    - National Politics- Non-Partisan Congressional Committees and Other Testimony, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 91:4)
    - National Politics- Non-Partisan Correspondence and Information, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 91:5)
    - Political Causes- Correspondence requesting Support, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 91:6)
    - Political Projects- Legislative Aide, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 91:7)
    - Political Workshop, Albany, New York and Voter Registration Drives, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 91:8)
    - Reapportionment of the 4th and 5th Congressional Districts in Georgia- Special Session, 1982 (Box-folder 91:9)
    - Small and Minority Owned Businesses in Georgia, 1976 (Box-folder 91:10)
    - Stationery used by Julian Bond, n.d. (Box-folder 91:11)
    - Strategy for 1971-1972 by Julian Bond, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 91:12)
    - Style Book for Form Letters, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 92:1)
    - Supreme Court Case Julian Bond v James Sloppy Floyd, 1966, 1 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 92:2)
    - Supreme Court Case Julian Bond v James "Sloppy" Floyd, 1966, 2 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 92:3)
    - Survey of Voters in 136th District, 1968, n.d. (Box-folder 92:4)
    - United States District Court For the Middle District of Alabama Case- NAACP v. Walter L. Allen, ca. 1973 (Box-folder 92:5)
      Regarding the exclusion of blacks from employment in the Alabama Department of Public Safety.
    - United States District Court For the Northern District of Georgia Case- United States v. the State of Georgia, 1976, n.d. (Box-folder 92:6)
    - United States House of Representatives Education Committee, 1972-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 92:7)
    - Voter Education Project Grant Recipients Letter concerning McGovern, n.d. (Box-folder 92:8)
    - Voter Registration and Tax Reform Bill- Correspondence of Bond with Elected Officials, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 92:9)
    - Voting- Statistical Record of African-Americans, 1976-1992 (Box-folder 92:10)
    - Voting Rights Act, 1969 (Box-folder 92:11)
    - Voting Rights Act Discrimination from Voter Education Project Files, 1967-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 92:12)
    - Voting Rights Act Violation in Talbotton, Georgia, 1969 (Box-folder 93:1)
    - Voting Rights- Alternative Voting Systems Manual Draft One prepared for the Southern Regional Council, 1998 July 29 (Box-folder 93:2)
    - Voting Rights- Cumulative Voting, 1994-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 93:3)
    - Voting Rights- Mississippi Voting Law, 1955-1962, n.d. (Box-folder 93:4)
    - Voting Rights- Proportional Voting, 1994-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 93:5)
    - Voting Rights- Redistricting and the Second Reconstruction, 1964-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 93:6)
    - Voting Rights- Symposium on Civil Rights in Mississippi, 1971-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 93:7)
    - Voting Rights- Voting Rights Act of 1965 Conference, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 93:8)
    - Voting Security and Voter Fraud, 2002-2004, n.d. (Box-folder 93:9)
  - Subseries B: Campaign for President 1976
    - Campaign Canvas Response Cards- Julian Bond for President, 1975, 1 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 94:1)
    - Campaign Canvas Response Cards- Julian Bond for President, 1975, 2 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 94:2)
    - Campaign Contributions- Julian Bond for President, 1975 (Box-folder 94:3)
    - Campaign Contributions- Julian Bond for President, 1975, 2 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 94:4)
    - Campaign Contribution Appeal- Julian Bond for President- Returned Mail, 1975, 1 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 94:5)
    - Campaign Contribution Appeal- Julian Bond for President- Returned Mail, 1975, 2 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 94:6)
    - Campaign Financing Materials Information, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 94:7)
    - Campaign Information for Julian Bond for President 1976, 1975 (Box-folder 94:8)
    - Campaign- Lists of Potential Contributors, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 94:9)
    - Campaign- Lists of Potential Contributors, 1975 (Box-folder 95:1)
    - Campaign Materials for Julian Bond for President 1976, 1975 (Box-folder 95:2)
    - Campaign Media Correspondence and Directories, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 95:3)
    - Campaign Newsletter Layout Designs, 1975, Oversize.
    - Campaign Press Releases, 1975 (Box-folder 95:4)
    - Campaign Volunteers, 1975 (Box-folder 95:5)
    - Campaign Volunteers, 1975, Cards. (Box-folder 95:6)
    - Computer Printout Results of Presidential Preference Primary, Fulton County, Georgia, 1976 May 4, Oversize.
    - Correspondence of James Bond, Presidential Campaign Manager, 1975 (Box-folder 95:7)
    - Correspondence concerning Bond's Presidential Campaign for 1976, 1974 December-1975 April (Box-folder 95:8)
    - Correspondence concerning Bond's Presidential Campaign for 1976, 1975 May-October (Box-folder 95:9)
    - Correspondence concerning Campaign Contributions, 1975 February-March, 1 of 4 folders. (Box-folder 95:10)
    - Correspondence concerning Campaign Contributions, 1975 April-May 6 (Box-folder 95:11)
    - Card File of Campaign Volunteers, 1975-1976 (Box 95-A)
    - Correspondence concerning Campaign Contributions, 1975 May 8-31, 3 of 4 folders. (Box-folder 96:1)
    - Correspondence concerning Campaign Contributions, 1975 June-August, 4 of 4 folders. (Box-folder 96:2)
    - Correspondence concerning Campaign Contributions, 1975, Cards. (Box-folder 96:3)
    - Correspondence requesting Bond Campaign Materials, 1975 (Box-folder 96:4)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- A States, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 96:5)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- California, 1975 (Box-folder 96:6)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- California, 1975 (Box-folder 96:7)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- C States and DC, 1975 (Box-folder 96:8)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- F States, 1975 (Box-folder 96:9)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- Georgia, 1975 (Box-folder 97:1)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- I, 1975 (Box-folder 97:2)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- K, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 97:3)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- "Ma" States, 1975 (Box-folder 97:4)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- Mi States, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 97:5)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- N States, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 97:6)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- New York, 1975 (Box-folder 97:7)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- O States, 1975 (Box-folder 97:8)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- P and R States, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 97:9)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- S States, 1975 (Box-folder 97:10)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- T and V States, 1975 (Box-folder 98:1)
    - Correspondence supporting Bond's Candidacy for President in 1976 (arranged alphabetically by the state of origin by Bond)- W States, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 98:2)
    - Draft Letters concerning Bond's Presidential Campaign, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 98:3)
    - Federal Election Commission- Julian Bond 1976 Campaign, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 98:4)
    - Presidential Primary Delegate Selection- New Primaries Memo from Ken Bode, 1975 (Box-folder 98:5)
    - Presidential Primary Delegate Selection Process, ca. 1972-1974 (Box-folder 98:6)
    - Presidential Primary Filing Dates and Presidential Preference and Delegate Selection Primaries for 1976 Document, 1975 (Box-folder 98:7)
- Series VII: Topical Files
  - Subseries A: General
    - Abortion and Birth Control, 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 98:8)
    - Affirmative Action, 1989-2003 (Box-folder 98:9)
    - Africa, 1968-2005 (Box-folder 98:10)
    - Africa- Darfur Region, Sudan Genocide, 2004 (Box-folder 98:11)
    - Alabama, 1949, 2002 (Box-folder 98:12)
    - American Bandstand Scrapbook, 1997 (Box-folder 98:13)
    - American Visionary Art Museum, 1998 (Box-folder 98:14)
    - Art and the Movement, 1998 (Box-folder 98:15)
    - Dr. Albert C. Barnes- Documents from Special Collections and Archives W.E.B. Du Bois Library, University of Massachusetts, Amherst (Copies), ca. 1926-1950 (Box-folder 99:1)
    - Dr. Albert C. Barnes ¨C Documents from Special Collections and Archives W.E.B. Du Bois Library, University of Massachusetts, Amherst (Copies), ca. 1950-1971 (Box-folder 99:2)
    - The Barnes Foundation, Possible Move of the Barnes Art Collection, 2003 (Box-folder 99:3)
    - The Barnes Foundation and Lincoln University, 1972-2005 (Box-folder 99:4)
    - Birmingham, Alabama, 1952, 1992, 1998 (Box-folder 99:5)
    - Black Conservatives, 1986-2002 (Box-folder 99:6)
    - Black Pioneers- the First One Hundred Black Certified Public Accountants, 1999 (Box-folder 99:7)
    - Black Power and the New Left, 1966 (Box-folder 99:8)
    - Book Reviews, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 99:9)
    - Bus Boycott, Montgomery, Alabama, [Children's Play], n.d. (Box-folder 99:10)
    - Census Data, 1960-2000 (Box-folder 99:11)
    - Civil Rights Films Project, 1995 (Box-folder 99:12)
    - Civil Rights Memorial, Montgomery, Alabama, ca. 1988-1989 (Box-folder 99:13)
    - Civil Rights Movement, Albany, Georgia, Freedom Ride and Protests, ca. 1960-1990 (Box-folder 99:14)
    - Civil Rights Movement, Atlanta, Georgia, Student Movement, 1960-1965, 1990 (Box-folder 100:1)
    - Civil Rights Movement-Biographies (alphabetical), 1964-1999 (Box-folder 100:2)
    - Civil Rights Movement- Chronologies, n.d. (Box-folder 100:3)
    - Civil Rights Movement Museum, Albany, Georgia, 1998 (Box-folder 100:4)
    - Civil Rights Movement- Research File, ca. 1932-1969, Copies. (Box-folder 100:5)
    - Civil Rights Movement- Research File- Mississippi Voter Education Project, [1963] (Box-folder 100:6)
    - Civil Rights Movement- Sit-Ins, 1960 (Box-folder 100:7)
    - Civil Rights Tour, 1993, 2006 (Box-folder 100:8)
    - Civil War and the Issue of Slavery, 2001 (Box-folder 100:9)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act- Shorthand Notebook, 1977 (Box-folder 100:10)
    - Computers- General and Personal Use, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 100:11)
    - Computers- Internet Access and Activism, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 100:12)
    - Conservatism and the Transformation of U.S. Policy, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 100:13)
    - Cuba, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 100:14)
    - Death Penalty, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 101:1)
    - Death Penalty, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 101:2)
    - Death Penalty- Delbert Tibbs Case, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 101:3)
    - Dixie, 1970-1991 (Box-folder 101:4)
    - W.E.B. Du Bois Memorial Site, 1969-1979, 1987 (Box-folder 101:5)
    - W.E.B. Du Bois Memorial Site, 1990-2002 (Box-folder 101:6)
    - Education and Race, 1989-2001 (Box-folder 101:7)
    - Elimination of Nuclear Weapons, 1969, 2000 (Box-folder 101:8)
    - Employment and Race, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 101:9)
    - Encyclopedia of Civil Rights in the United States, 1996 (Box-folder 101:10)
    - Louis Farrakhan and the Million Man March, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 101:11)
    - James Forman (1928-2005), Death of, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 101:12)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- Detroit Police Department- Records concerning Julian Bond, 1960s, Copies made in 1991. (Box-folder 102:1)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies 1 of 11 folders. (Box-folder 102:2)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (2 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 102:3)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (3 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 102:4)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (4 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 102:5)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (5 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 102:6)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (6 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 103:1)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (7 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 103:2)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests- FBI Civil Rights Division- Records concerning The Atlanta Constitution and The Atlanta Journal, 1960s, Copies (8 of 11 folders). (Box-folder 103:3)